It's my life, it's your
life Fighting for tomorrow,
go catch what you really want I want more,
anyone more Come on, walkin'
up the door It's my life,
it's your life Run like
a wind, jump high, yeah,
yeah I know you're strong Believe you can
achieve your call Let's keep on going,
how not dance?
Let's do it again, you
know what I mean, baby.
No one can make my dream come true!
Don't you feel it?
I really don't know what is
Something is testing me every day.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away.
I know I never wanna come back here.
Hey, let's go.
Let's fly away the great
end of the unknown rules.
Standing up, blowing up.
My dream is getting wilder.
I'm not afraid, beat me, hit me.
I will never turn around.
Another day, another chance.
You know it's never too late.
If I can do it, so can you only without.
It's my life, it's your life.
Party for tomorrow, go
get what you really want.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the door.
It's my life, it's your life.
Run like a wind, jump high, yeah, yeah.
I know you're strong.
Believe you can achieve your goal.
Let's keep on going, roaring.
It's my life, it's your life.
Fighting for your eyes that
I want, but your weary ones.
I want more, anyone more,
come on, open up the gate.
It's my life, it's your light,
shine like a star to be good.
I know you're strong, trust that
you can't achieve your best.
Let's keep on going out of day.
You make my day every day.
How dare you stop me,
you know I've been looking
forward to this smashing law.
for sculling, so move!
No way!
It's the color of the
Supreme King's Haki glashing!
That brat can use it too?
Straw Hats.
You can use it, just like I thought.
What?
You're kidding!
You knocked everyone out
cold on your own, little guy?
That's powerful Haki.
Well... Haki?
And it's the Supreme King's Haki too.
That's great
Those with the quality of the
Supreme King stand above all others.
To Flamingo, you were
chosen by heaven itself;
your Haki is the proof.
Now.
Let's have a test to see if
you're a real man or not!
Are there any people who you want to kill?
Do you want me to give you
the strength to take revenge?
People I want to kill
There's plenty of them.
Duffy is of a completely
different caliber than you.
His birth nurtured a madness inside him.
His fate fed him endless fury.
They changed this man
into a perfect demon.
The ultimate evil made to grasp
the world and tear it asunder.
So what?
Who cares?
Let's go!
Ahhhhh!
Ahhhh!
Go to hell!
Bingo!
Ahhhh!
Tofie's madness will tear
apart this world at the seams.
Eagle!
Batsuka!
Athlete!
Take Stinkable Whale!
What is this stuff?
This is just sad.
A nobody like you never had
a chance of beating Doofy.
Let me go!
I got an ass kicking to get!
Dolfi, go ahead.
I'll keep Straw Hat right here.
Don't let that squirrely little
bastard try any more tricks.
Hey, don't ignore me.
We were having a fight.
Flo can't even move, you big evil jerk.
I said you'd get your turn, didn't I?
Let me go, you weirdo.
Why are you so icky?
It's stinky.
It's no use, what that's not right?
Armament Haki should work on logia.
Ain't that funny?
But what makes you so sure?
I'm a logia type, whatever I am,
you can't win if you can't touch me.
Rubber tummy, Straw Hat—ignore him!
He's trash.
Just paper mache covered in snot.
Why
did you just call me when I was a kid?
I was offered the heart throne.
But
why would I want to be
associated with all of you?
You're buffoons!
Your mouth still works if nothing else.
You're half dead already—what do you know?
It's taking us like me.
Run the family and the family run stress,
Rosa, and now we're
running it into the ground!
Just like you, you bastard!
Okay,
you
brat—you'd
better listen up! Step aside.
up step aside
I'm going to teach you a lesson, Law.
Duffy is king.
His will is absolute,
and we all respect that.
However, there's no hierarchy
between him and the four top executives.
We're equals, okay.
You know why that is?
Because one day, 30-something years ago,
a gift fell from heaven, and the
four of us were smart enough.
to see it for what it was and nurture it.
We gave him the power he deserved
and turned him into what he is today,
a true champion of evil.
You said they tried to kill
you when you went to Marijua?
But you brought your father's head.
What's the deal?
Anyway, we're all happy you
made it back here alive.
It's a miracle.
You belong with us.
Huh? Doofy.
Doofy, your power proves you
have the quality of a conqueror.
Doofy, we support you in
everything that you do.
Doofy, all we ask of you is that
you show us your wildest dreams.
Is something wrong, Duffy?
What is that bruise on your forehead?
Some street thug did it.
The jerk.
I wish he was dead.
Okay, I understand.
Huh?
What do you want?
Just one little question.
You're the guy who roughed up
Dolfi earlier, aren't you? Oh.
That little brat?
I just teased him a little.
What happened?
Did some jackass hurt you again?
No, I just tripped on a crack in the road.
How awful.
Where exactly is this town?
Oh, I see. Yep.
We're gonna have to do
something about this.
Listen, Duffy, you're a king.
That means no one is
allowed to defy your will.
And if they do, we'll stomp them out.
You may not feel like a king just yet.
But one day I swear.
You'll be the ruler of all the seas.
We always had faith in Duffy as our king.
And we instilled that faith
in his underlings too.
And now,
that vision has become a
reality because we saw Duffy for
what he truly was and upheld
our devotion to his cause.
Just like a real family.
And that's how Duffy treats us in return.
But nothing else to say.
Or maybe you remember that
my mucus is flammable.
I can shut you up for good whenever
I like with a flick of a...
What a joke.
Only an idiot like you would
buy into that crap, Treble.
His dream is everything, but you
only matter so long as you serve it.
What did you just say to me?
Take a good look at yourself.
It's all just a lie.
You act like you're some chief of
staff, but I can see the truth.
You're a clown.
Doflamingo's puppet.
A clown!
A puppet, you say!
Unforgivable!
Stop!
You're falling into a trap! Room!
They're inside his room!
He was barely alive in the first place,
and now he's covered from
head to toe in my mucus.
What the hell is he gonna do?
Come on, open your mouth already.
Let him go!
Or do I need to do it for you?
I'm shoving this down your throat!
Time for you to say goodbye, law!
Stop it!
Don't forget, I'm a captain too.
If I leave you and Doflamingo,
Forrestraw had to defeat alone,
I'd be abandoning my pride.
You're stuck on the ground
like a miserable worm!
What pride do you have left?
I'm so sick of you!
Just die!
Tucked!
What the...
No!
Sturban! Blame!
Begin!
Is something wrong, Leo?
What's up little bros!
Started looking towards
the palace all of a sudden.
I I don't quite understand why,
but it feels like a giant weight has
just been lifted off my chest. Huh?
Save it.
No time for fuzzy feelings now.
I know we just destroyed the factory, but
we gotta haul ass, and we'll get wrecked.
That's kind of weird.
I wonder all that goop and stuff,
he was actually super skinny?
That's why my punch couldn't hit him?
Not some secret ability?
Damn you, Lord!
I tried to warn you.
Lord, you can die with me!
You've lost it!
Put away the fire!
See you in hell, Lord!
The whole palace just burst into flames!
I see them!
They're coming here!
Loopyland!
Do you think he'll be okay?
We have to back him up somehow, Cub. Yeah.
We probably shouldn't.
In fact, we'd likely just get in his way.
Look close.
That man with Luffy is a
warlord like Doflamingo.
That's Trafalgar Law.
And he's in pretty bad shape.
Robin!
Luffy!
Down here!
Let me take Traffy!
Robin! Good idea! He's hurt!
And Traffy held his own against Mingo!
Oh, no! His arm!
I've got you!
Dance, look! Spider-Man!
What happened to Lawland's arm?
We'll get through this.
Don't worry. I've got you.
Nico Robin.
I don't want you butting in on our fight.
The man's still breathing, isn't he?
Then I'm not done with it.
Doflamingo!
Leave Traffy alone!
This is our fight now!
This'll finish you.
All right, Kuma Kuma!
Bullet strength!
Oh, quit!
Damn it!
You have to flee!
Robin! Run away!
Precious Metal Axe!
It's Cabbage! Forgive me.
Up till now, I was sleeping.
You still haven't cleaned up this mess?
Come on, Straw Hat!
Hey, Cabbage!
Take everyone and get off the plateau!
Are you kidding me?
Why would I do that when
Doflamingo's standing right there?
Let me fight him just one blow!
I'm leaving my friends in your hands,
my goodness—he trusts me,
not only trust, respect!
So
a straw
hat is my fan;
a favor?
favor from a fan?
Then I can't say no!
Portolomeo is still on the lower level.
We could use his power. Let's go find him.
Can you do anything? Leo!
Those cuts look pretty ragged.
If I can sew him up, that's something.
That could work.
Then I can heal him.
My watering can should fix
him up, good idea, Princess!
Thank you, but first we should
all get to safety, like Lucy said.
Hey, Bortula, Mayo!
alright a die for mr.
Zoro till the end of the line are you
listening to me you You're a nitwit!
You should stop being so selfish.
You're wasting precious time.
Your poor friend Law is
suffering because he can't die.
Let me put him out of his misery
if you want to kill him so bad,
then you could do it after you beat me.
Seems you're worn out already?
Wouldn't you rather just take a break?
You're as bad off as me.
I saw that special move traffic in before?
There's no way that didn't mess you up!
Ah!
Bazooka!
You're fast, I'll give you that.
But your attacks don't
have nearly enough weight.
Overheat!
It brings back memories.
Crocodile was defeated.
And they're telling us a
captain from Navy HQ did it.
Not a chance.
There must be a catch.
Look, it's gotta be him.
Why else would his
bounty jump up like that?
Find out about this pirate group.
I've never heard their name.
Monkey D.
Then you showed up at Marine
Ford, falling from the sky.
You've done well to survive this
long, but your luck runs out today!
Stop!
I didn't expect you to wake up yet.
Are you all right?
Put me down.
Leave me here.
And why would you want that?
For the past 13 years,
the only thing I've been living
for is a chance to kill Doflamingo.
I've done everything I
can, but I'm all worn out.
So now, all that's left is
to have faith in Straw Hat.
But if he's gonna win, then
I wanna be there to watch.
By the same token,
if he doesn't win, then I need to be
there so that I can die along with him.
I'm the one who got Strahl had
involved in this whole conflict.
That's why I have to see it through.
So leave me.
I don't know what to say.
Treffy, captains of a true pirate
alliance are on equal footing.
Luffy's here of his
own free will. You see?
If he didn't want to fight, he'd refuse.
I'm begging you, please, leave me!
I suppose there's no
talking you out of it.
Nico Robin, you go on ahead.
Cabbage!
I can't grant you a
quest if it'll kill you.
I'll stay here, too.
I don't want to hear any complaints.
If you do die today, it'll be after me.
miss robin hey we should go or the lameo
is waiting he made a path go here please
No!
Third gear!
Let's go!
Come, come!
Grizzly Mother!
You're wide open!
Trying to hurry so Law's
attack won't go to waste.
But even if you do defeat
them, how long will that take?
There's a one-hour limit,
but it's not that simple.
That's how long until the
birdcage fully collapses.
but you have to think there's
plenty of sick and elderly
people out there and babies
as well not everyone can run
the vulnerable will fall
victim quickly i'm sure
it will only take 30 minutes
for the fatalities to
start piling up after
40 minutes have passed i
imagine we'll be able to
hear the screams close by.
Then after 50 minutes, the kingdom
will be painted red, as if it were
covered in crushed tomatoes.
And then the screams will
die out, just one hour until
only silence remains.
You have nothing to do with this kingdom.
You don't owe these people
anything.
And yet the deaths today rest
entirely on your shoulders.
They would still be smiling
if you hadn't come here.
My kingdom would still be at peace.
That wasn't peace.
It It was all built on lies!
There's no place in the world
where everyone prospers.
It's a waste of time
trying to save them all.
You're just a pirate passing through.
Why are you trying to play hero?
You dare pick a fight with me, Straw Hat.
That's not true!
You're the one picking a fight with me!
You made so many of my friends cry.
And you made my crewmates angry, too.
You'll keep hurting people
until you're stopped.
It's time for me to step up.
I won't let anyone else die!
I'M KICKING YOUR ASS AND
WRECKING YOUR Baratie CAGE!
Alright...FOURTH GEAR!